Metal Cardbot Commentary!
Parting and Reunion
Hey, guys! Jun here.
Let's watch another episode of Metal Cardbot together.
It's "Metal Cardbot Commentary" time!
Mega Trucker, setup!
I'm Mega Trucker!
I'm excited to do another one of these!
Great to see you again, Mega Trucker!
Today's episode is about the first time
Blue Cop's identity was revealed.
Let's watch the episode together!
Huh? What was that? What's going on out here?!
Huh??
Uh, Uncle Edo...
Stay away from Jun!
W-wait!
Uncle Edo, were you in the repair shop?!
I dozed off while working late... then I was woken up by a loud noise outside!
Wow! Being able to run like that while holding Jun!
Does Edo work out?
I've never thought to ask him about his workout routine.
Next time I see him, I'll have to challenge him to tug-of-war!
Uh... Even for Uncle Edo, don't you think that might be a bit much?
Please stop it, this is not safe!
What did you say?!
I'm tired and thirsty... Could you get me some coffee?
Yes, sir.
So you really can make coffee!
It's a basic skill for surviving on planet Earth.
One sugar and no cream, okay?
Yes, sir!
Here you are.
Augh, why is it so sweet?!
Hahaha! That Blue Cop!
You're telling me he can't even make coffee?!
Mega Trucker! Do you know how to make coffee, too?
Of course!
Just get a mouthful of coffee, water, and sugar
and gulp it right down! How'dya like that?
Huh?!
Maybe if you had a coffee maker for a mouth...?
There's a bad traffic jam.
Augh, but I'm in a hurry!
I'll do my best.
Wait, what are you going to do?
Woah, woah, woah! Watch out!
Oh!
Hang on, stop the car!
Come on, I said stop!
Blue Cop, don't you think...
you were driving a little fast?
Jun!
Y'think he's been in his fair share of racing competitions?
Mega Trucker!
Blue Cop might be upset if he hears this!
Hey~
How else can you dodge traffic like that while going so fast!?
Eh...
If something happens to Jun, how will I explain it to his parents?
So, you should leave. Go back to your planet!
That was the wobbly truck!
Oh man... was the driver dozing off?
Oh no! We need to go alert the train, quick!
Blue Cop... where are you...
You wouldn't mind if I used the siren in this situation, would you?
Blue Cop!
Scoot over. I'll help you with that!
Just a little more!
It was really scary when that truck got overturned...!
If you get tired while driving, you should pull over and take a break!
That's right!
No matter how urgent the situation, you should never drive while drowsy!
Hey Jun,
who are you talking to?
Uh...
Wouldn't it be good for everyone to hear?
Well, how was that?
Blue Cop and I parted ways for a little while,
but we met again and were able to solve the crisis together!
Now then, please look forward to the next "Metal Cardbot Commentary"!